YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
时间轴：godwuwen 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
翻译： 饿得慌  非燕  阿蘅  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
校对： 谢尔顿赛  佩妮猫    后期：孤帆 字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二十集
切斯特  你怎么还没换衣服
Chester, you're not even dressed.
-还有15分钟就到预约时间了  -嘘
- The reservation is in 15 minutes. - Shh!
他回来了
He's back.
每晚八点  分秒不差
Every night at exactly 8:00 p.m.,
那个西装革履的金发男子都会出现
the well-dressed blond man appears.
恰克和乔安要等急了
Chuck and Joanne are going to be waiting.
你不懂
You don't understand!
每天晚上  他都如出一辙
Every night, he does this.
一天都不落
Every single night.
周三
他走出大楼
He steps out of this building,
迈七步  停下
walks exactly seven paces, stops,
然后微笑
and smiles.
周四
周五
亲爱的  你别吓我好吗
Honey, I am worried about you.
他是不是想和某人接头
Is he trying to communicate with someone?
他是不是想要联络我
Is he trying to communicate with me?
他为什么要这么做啊
Why is he doing this?!
除了不让你在家里放屁之外
But aside from not being able to fart in the apartment,
-和昆茵相处得怎么样  -很不错啊
- how's living with Quinn? - Oh, it's great.
没错
Yep.
和昆茵住在一起感觉很棒
Living with Quinn is great.
简直就是妙趣横生  妙不可言
Great, great, great... great.
到底是有多苦
So how bad is it?
苦不堪言啊
Pretty bad.
昨天晚上
Last night,
我八点钟刚放完屁回来
I had just come back 8:00 fart.
-好  -接着说
- Sure. - Go on.
信箱还是空的
Still no mail.
邮差每天只送一次信吧
I think they only deliver it once a day.
我搬进来之前  把自己的东西都卖了
Hey, listen, when I moved in here, I sold all my stuff
因为我知道你希望家里保持原样
because I know you like your place as is,
我对此完全没意见
and I was totally fine with that.
我只有一个小要求
Just one little thing:
能不能不用你的咖啡杯
would it be okay if instead of using your coffee mugs,
换用我的
we use mine?
不行
No.
巴尼  她为了你把自己的东西都卖了
Barney, she got rid of all of her stuff for you.
我知道问题出在哪儿了
Oh, I see what this is really about.
不就是杯子嘛
Yeah, mugs.
咖啡
Coffee?
茶
Tea?
信仰冲突
Religion.
问题在你  你打从心眼里觉得
This is about the fact that you don't think
这段恋情不会长久
this relationship is gonna last.
所以你才不想丢掉自己的东西
That's why you don't want to throw anything out.
因为你们早晚会分手
Because when that inevitable breakup comes,
到时你也可以省得买新的了
you don't want to buy new mugs.
所以不管跟谁谈恋爱
That's why I've never thrown anything out
我从来不扔东西
for any relationship ever.
没错吧  亲爱的
Isn't that right, honey?
哎呦  没错  我是单身
Oh, that's right. I'm alone.
莉莉  你听我解释
Lily, here's the thing.
那是我家
It's my apartment,
作为男人  我要维护自己的统治权
and I need to assert my dominance as a man.
千万不要对女人
Don't ever say that...
说这种话
to any girl ever.
已经晚了
Too late.
你刚跟我说什么
What did you just say to me?
-她为了你连家都不要了  -亏你说得出口
- She gave up her apartment for you! - You said that to her?!
我受够了
Okay, you know what?
我没必要坐在着让你们女人讨伐
I don't have to sit here and take this from you ladies.
我要去泰德家了
I'm going to Ted's.
男人的地盘
The man cave,
可以随心所欲做自己
where guys can be guys.
-维护你的统治权  -你懂不懂尊重女人啊
- Assert your dominance? - It's like you have no respect for women.
-你脑子进水啦  -你可是女人生的啊
- What is wrong with you? - You have a mother!
怎么连你们也这样
You guys, too?
我要去舒缓一下我郁闷的心情
I'm going to the Y for a shvitz.
别  哥们  慢着
No, dude, hold on.
你哪儿也不准去
You're not going anywhere.
今天是星战三部曲时间
It's trilogy time.
卫斯理大学
2000年
星战三部曲时间的由来是这样的
Kids, here's the deal with trilogy time:
故事发生在很久以前
It all started a long time ago
在一间遥远的男生寝室里
in a dorm room far, far away.
哥们  咱们期末要是经济学挂了
Dude, if we fail this econ final,
那下半辈子就别想...
for the rest of our lives we're not gonna be able to...
咱们就不知道该怎么...
We won't know how to...
你知道经济学是什么吗
Do you even know what econ is?
一头雾水  咱们死定了
No idea. We're screwed.
在这种窘境之下  只有一件事可做
But there's only one thing left to do at at time like this.
一口气看完《星球大战》三部曲
Watch the entire Star Wars trilogy all the way through
因为我五年没这么干过了
because I haven't done that in, like, five years.
哥们  你不能这么堕落
Dude, you can't let that happen.
你起码要每隔三年就要看一遍
If you're not trilling it at least once every three years,
不然黑暗面就要获胜了
the Dark Side wins.
好  那我们做个约定吧
Okay, let's make a pact.
无论如何  每隔三年
No matter what, every three years,
我们都要一起看一遍三部曲
we sit down and trill it up big time.
同意吗
Agreed?
同意[格里多]
A-Greedo.
格里多 《星球大战》中的赏金猎人
2003年
2003, I mean...
那时的我们会怎么样呢
What's that gonna be like?
《都市日报》
总统戈尔签署一个历史性的议案
泰德
Hey, Ted.
发型不错
Sweet hair.
我告诉过你  我的头发总有一天会停止自然卷
I told you it would eventually stop growing out
并变得长发飘飘
and start growing down.
话说  我现在执笔设计另一栋摩天大楼
Anyway, I'm just working on designing yet another skyscraper.
而我现在手提公文包
And I'm carrying this briefcase
因为我现在是个成功的律师
because now I'm a successful lawyer...
我喜欢这剧情
I like that.
我能做个改动吗
Can I make one adjustment?
并留着威武的小胡子
...with a cool mustache.
漂亮
Nice.
谁知道呢  到那时
And who knows, by then,
你和莉莉说不定都订婚了
you and Lily might be engaged.
订婚
Engaged?
兄弟  我一定会更胜一筹
Bro, I'm gonna do way better than that.
怀孕真是太有意思了
Ah, being pregnant is so much fun.
我还想再生四个孩子
I want to do this four more times.
宝贝  自从我能
Oh, baby, how do you feel after
挣大钱养家糊口
spending all day working on your art,
你整天窝在家里创作艺术后  感觉如何
since I make enough to support us both financially?
欲求不满
Horny.
我希望你别介意  泰德
I hope we don't bother you, Ted,
因为即便我们结了婚  有了娃
because even though we're married and pregnant,
还睡成人双层床  也很合情合理嘛
it still makes sense that we all share adult-sized bunk beds.
想看《星球大战》吗
So, Star Wars?
当然  我可以傍晚才去上班
Sure, I don't have to be at work until late afternoon-ish
因为我老板不介意我
because my boss appreciates that
通宵喝酒  还...
I like to stay up late drinking and...
跟我们的乐队一起玩摇滚
rocking out with our band.
有人刚说玩摇滚吗
Did someone say rocking out?
哇  那个靓妞是谁
Whoa, who's the babe?
这正是最棒的部分
That's the best part.
伙计们  你们还记得我的超辣女友吧
Guys, you remember my awesome girlfriend
在遇见我之前  一直都守身如玉哦
who was a virgin until we met?
我叫赖安娜
My name's Rhiannon,
就像史蒂薇·尼克斯歌里唱的
like the Stevie Nicks song.
我虽性感  但是绿色环保的森女型
I'm hot, but in a crunchy, earthy kind of way.
忘说了  我是英国人哟
Oh, and I'm from England.
真不错
Nice.
好了  该看《星球大战》了
Okay, Star Wars time.
但首先  我们即兴来一曲吧
But first, we jam.
幸好我前三年有花时间
Good thing I spent the last three years
练习用耍酷刷吉他
learning to wail on guitar.
宝贝
Babe.
我们乐队的表演将供不应求
Yup, our band is gonna be in demand.
幸好  我们有求必应
And luckily, there'll be plenty of supply.
"供"给  需"求"
Supply? Demand?
伙计  你有注意到我们的用词吗
Dude, do you realize what we just did?
我们居然用到经济学
We used econ.
期末考我们肯定名列前茅
We're gonna ace this final.
结果我们双双吃鸭蛋
We both got zeroes.
兄弟
Oh, dude,
2003年肯定会精彩绝伦
2003 is gonna be awesome.
(现实情况)
是《满足》吗
"Satisfaction"?
英国滚石乐队作品
是《十字面包歌》
"Hot Cross Buns."
英文儿歌
继续努力  兄弟
Well, keep it up, bro.
那你准备好观看星战三部曲了吗
So, you ready to watch the trilogy?
不知道
I don't know.
我之前真以为  现在的我会成为一名律师
I mean, I really thought that by now I'd be a lawyer
还留着威武的小胡子
with a kick-ass mustache,
可我现在还没考进法学院
but I still haven't even gotten into law school,
而且胡子长得参差不齐
and my facial hair just grows in patchy.
又红又散
Just red and patchy.
别不爽了  你的生活没那么糟
Come on. Your life's not that bad.
伙计  我在班尼路当店长
Dude, I manage a Structure.
Structure现名为Express Men's
Victoria's Secre旗下的男士休闲品牌  价位类似美国的班尼路
但你买背心可以打九折  相当不错了
But you get 10% off vests. That's something.
-那些背心是还不错  可...  -对啊
- The vests are pretty sweet, but, look... - Yeah.
我和莉莉还没结婚
Lily and I aren't married.
莉莉也没怀有孩子
We don't have a baby on the way.
至少我们现在的住处不错
But we did get the cool apartment.
可我们根本住不起
That we can barely afford.
我是说  现在的生活
I mean, I don't see any way that our lives
比三年前的好不到哪儿去
are better now than they were three years ago.
真的吗  马修  再仔细想想
Oh, really, Marshall? Nothing comes to mind?
对了  伙计们  这位是丽莎
By the way, guys, this is Lisa.
以后你们会常常见到她的
You'll be seeing a lot more of Lisa.
然而她却再也没有出现过了
And they never saw her again.
帅吧
Whassaaaa!
好吧
Okay,
三年前  我们满怀希冀
three years ago, we had this whole fantasy
幻想我们日后的生活会变得多棒
about how great our lives were gonna be,
可事实不尽如人意
and it didn't pan out.
但我告诉你  三年后
But I'm telling you, three years from now,
当我们在2006年看星战三部曲时
when we're watching the trilogy in 2006,
那时我们的生活一定精彩绝伦
our lives are gonna be awesome.
《都市日报》
总统迪安平静发表全国演说
你好  泰德
Ah, hello, Ted.
我现在是一名环境律师
I'm an environmental lawyer now.
当然  这个领域不能赚大钱
Sure, it's not the most lucrative field,
可幸运的是  我在《幸运之轮》
but luckily I have the cash and prizes
蝉联了七周冠军宝座
from my historic seven-week run
赢了不少现金和奖品
on Wheel of Fortune...
《幸运之轮》  美国最火的智力答题游戏电视节目
我能稍做改动吗
Can I just make one little adjustment?
我被女王陛下授予了爵士爵位
...for which I was knighted by Her Majesty, the Queen.
艾得仁夫人
Ah, Lady Aldrin.
马修先生
Oh, Sir Marshall.
我迫不及待想搬去
I cannot wait to get a house
离你父母近点的地方住
down the street from your parents
这样我们能多跟你母亲亲近
so we can be close to your mom,
而且我现在跟她超合得来哟
whom I get along with now.
甚好  甚好
Good, good.
最棒的部分来了
But here's the best part.
赖安娜  快
Rhiannon, hurry!
人家不会因为我设计了这个歌剧院
Just because I designed the opera house
就非得等我们到场后才开演
doesn't mean they'll hold the curtain for us.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
他们一定会等的
Of course it does.
慢慢来  亲爱的
Take your time, my love.
伙计们  又是我
Hey, guys, it's me again.
我和上次差不多
I'm pretty much the same as last time,
只是现在我家财万贯雍容华贵
only now I'm super-rich and fancy.
还有  这次我是法国人哟
而且我们还住在一起  也合情合理
And it still makes sense that we all live together.
你呢  巴尼
What about you, Barney?
对2006年有期许吗
Any predictions for 2006?
是啊  想象一下
Oh, yeah. Picture it.
对了  伙计们  这位是乔迪
By the way, guys, this is Jody.
以后你们会常常见到她的
You'll be seeing a lot more of Jody.
然而她却再也没有出现过了
And they never saw her again.
帅吧
Whassaaaa!
那和你现在的生活有什么区别啊
How is that any different from your life right now?
没区别  我是肯德基  宝贝
It's not. I'm KFC, baby.
上校的食谱  岂能说改就改
You don't mess with the Colonel's recipe.
我就要维持原样
I want things to stay exactly the same,
但辣妹可以轮着换
but with a different hottie.
因为巴尼绝不吃回头妞
'Cause Barney don't slurp no sloppy seconds,
也不让妞吃回头"鸡"
especially his own.
好的  归根结底
Okay, the bottom line is
日子一定会蒸蒸日上的
things are gonna get better.
我只是一心想进法学院
Well, all I care about is getting into law school.
会进的
You will.
2006年肯定会精彩绝伦
2006 is gonna be awesome.
(现实情况)
瞧瞧现在
And look what happened.
你进了法学院
You got into law school,
我当初就说你会进的
just like I said you would.
看  情况也没那么糟
See, things aren't so bad.
可莉莉离开了我
Lily left me.
而我这辈子不可能有小胡子了
And now I'll never have a mustache.
宝贝  你在这里啊
Baby, there you are.
我今天一整天都在想着
I have spent all day thinking about all the naughty,
要跟你"干"一些淘气的事
naughty things you and I are gonna do
好让马修振作起来
to cheer up Marshall.
比如说
Like what?
你们先聊吧  好吗
Uh, I'll let you guys hang out, okay?
我去...
Um, I'll just be...
卧室里等你吧
waiting in the bedroom.
抱歉  我不是故意
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I didn't mean that
说得好像我跟泰德要"干"什么事情一样
to sound like Ted and I are gonna do a kind of thing.
好  好
Okay, okay.
回见
See you.
马修  会过去的
Marshall, this will pass.
相信我
Trust me.
三年后
Three years from now...
公文包  律师
Briefcase, lawyer,
爵士爵位  小胡子
knighthood, mustache,
一切都和从前一样
all that stuff from before.
恭喜你  兄弟
Congratulations, bro.
也恭喜你  泰德
And congratulations to you too, Ted,
能拴住如此佳人
for locking this down.
想来也怪
You know, it's weird,
我从未想过要结婚
I never thought I would get married,
可你说服了我
but you talked me into it.
更确切地说  是你"睡"服了我
Or rather, banged me into it.
你的床上功夫棒极了
You're so good in bed, ooh.
你这算哪门子的安慰啊
How is this helping me?
快到重点了
I'm getting to it.
三年后  不光莉莉会回来  而且...
In three years, not only will Lily be back, but...
和完美男人喜结连理
It's so nice to be married to a wonderful guy
并孕育他的孩子真好
and be carrying his child.
泰德  你太过乐观了吧
I think you're being kind of optimistic, Ted.
我能稍做改动吗
Can I make one little adjustment?
和完美男人喜结连理
It's so nice to be married to a wonderful guy
并孕育他的孩子真好
and carrying his child,
孩子他爸  快过来
and here he is now.
各位  我来给你们介绍
Guys, I want you to meet
这位人渣  他叫特雷
some douchey guy named Trey.
你好  兄弟
'Sup, bro?
我都不晓得到底更喜欢他哪点
I don't know what I love more:
是浓密的胡子
his thick mustache
还是他的潮帽
or his trucker hat.
你知道我讨厌那种帽子
You know I hate those hats.
那你肯定也会讨厌这张声波图
Then you're really gonna hate this sonogram.
不要啊
Nooo...
戴着潮帽的宝宝  太妙了
A baby in a trucker hat. That's awesome.
总之  泰德是对的
Anyway, Ted's right.
2009年肯定会精彩绝伦
2009's gonna rule.
对了  各位  这是玛雅
By the way, guys, this is Maya.
以后你们会常常见到她的
You'll be seeing a lot more of Maya.
然而她却再也没有出现过了
And they never saw her again.
帅吧
Whassaaaa!
好了  说真的
Okay, seriously,
2009年  我们九周年的喝酒小聚时
at least tell me you're gonna change the what will by then
好歹你也换句台词吧
be nine-year-old beer commercial reference.
拜托大哥
I mean, come on.
你真的不想
There's got to be at least one way
改变一下你一成不变的生活吗
that you'd like the future to be different.
倒是想改变一件事
I guess there is one thing.
各位  这是玛雅
By the way, guys, this is Maya.
以后你们会常常见到她的
You'll be seeing a lot more of Maya.
不是因为她胸前的雄伟
And not because of these these.
而是因为背后也雄伟
Because of these.
后胸  原本只属于传教士式的
Back boobs-- the visual stimulation
视觉刺激  在后入式时也能享受到了
of missionary meets the emotional detachment of doggy-style.
专利申请中
Patent pending.
帅吧
Whassaaaa!
马修  重点是
The point is, Marshall,
三年后的今天  万事会更好
this time in three years, everything is gonna be great.
(现实情况)
瞧  莉莉回来了
See? Lily came back.
当然了  我和罗宾最后还是分手了
Of course, Robin and I didn't end up together.
但我确实有个未婚妻
But I did get engaged.
可惜她最后一秒落跑了
And left at the altar.
我还开了自己的建筑公司
But I did start my own architectural firm.
可惜两个月后倒闭了
And it failed after a few months.
-能把电影放起吗  -好
- Can we put the movie on, please? - Yeah.
当然可以
Sure, buddy.
对了  罗宾呢
Hey, by the way, where is Robin?
在2009年的夏天
In the summer of 2009,
巴尼和罗宾在搞地下恋情
Barney and Robin were secretly dating.
巴尼说罗宾在上剪纸补习班
Barney said she's taking some extension class in how to decoupage,
巴尼也在同一栋楼里  上另一个剪纸补习班
and Barney's taking a different decoupage class in the same building.
所以他们有次一次打车回来
That's why they shared that cab that one time.
当年我们真是白痴
We were idiots.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你说巴尼·斯丁森在上剪纸补习班啊
You're saying that Barney Stinson is at a decoupage class?
那我们可以用他的大电视来看《星球大战》啦
That means we can watch Star Wars on his giant TV!
冲啊  老兄
Punch it, Chewy!
你从剪纸班回来了
You're back from decoupage.
什么剪纸班
What's decoupage?
对  我在那里打过一次车
Oh, uh, yeah, I took that cab there that one time.
等等
Hold on.
进来
Come on in.
我们能不能在这里看星战三部曲
We were hoping we could watch the trilogy here.
没问题  不过...
Uh, sure. But, uh...
先去我卧室的窗户往外看
first go look out my, uh, bedroom window.
有个...
There's a, uh...
裸女...
naked lady, uh...
在迷你弹簧床上乱蹦...
jumping up and down on a mini-trampoline
那间公寓就在...
in the apartment across the, uh...
对面街
street.
让我出来
Get me out of this thing!
没时间啊
There's no time!
巴尼  我还没准备好公开关系
Barney, I am not ready for them to find out about us.
那你就得乖乖待到三部曲播完啦
Then you're gonna have to stay in there for the entire trilogy.
别担心  才六个小时二十二分而已
Don't worry. It's only 382 minutes.
死阿宅
Nerd!
大家觉得  三年后我们会如何
So, where do you guys think we'll be in three years?
到时就是2012年了
It'll be 2012.
很简单啊
That's an easy one.
各位  这是索菲娅
Guys, this is Sophia.
以后你们会常常...
You'll be seeing a lot more of...
太神奇了
Okay, that is so weird.
我刚试着想用一下星战里的原力
I was just trying to use the force.
会不会是我的原力没让啤酒
Do you think instead of making a beer
从冰箱里飞出来  却让这个灯摔碎了啊
fly out of the fridge, I made that lamp break??
不是你的原力  就是风暴兵弄的了
Either that or the stormtrooper did.
帝国风暴兵才不会那么做
Oh, the stormtrooper would never do that.
他知道那个灯价值一千二
He knows that lamp costs $1,200.
对了  既然都是自己人
Anyway, while it's just us guys,
我问你们一点事
let me ask you something:
我们都幻想过和穿着
we've all had that same fantasy
风暴兵服的女人上床  对吧
in a stormtrooper costume, right?
-没  -从来没有
- Mmm, no. - Never.
兄弟们
Guys...
周围没有女人  就我们几兄弟
come on, no girls around, just us bros.
直说无妨
Safe space.
放下虚伪  实话实说
Let's stop being polite and start gettin' real.
风暴兵的性幻想
Stormtrooper fantasy.
每个男人都幻想过  对吧
Every guy's had that one, right?
-没想过  -没有没有
- Not even once, no. - No, no, no.
那我才是怪胎吗
So I'm the weird one?
-对  -对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
没错
Yeah.
你呢  泰德
How about you, Ted?
三年后  你的生活
How's your life gonna be different
会有什么不同
in, whatever, three years?
和以前一样
Oh, you know, the usual.
遇见真爱  结婚生子
Gonna meet a nice girl and get married.
虽说我每年都老生常谈  不过
I mean, I know I say that every year, but...
老实说  2012年我就满34岁了
let's be honest, in 2012, I'll be 34.
如果到时候我还没结婚
If it still hasn't happened for me by then,
肯定是我这人自身的毛病了
something is seriously wrong with me!
(现实情况)
肯定是我这人自身的毛病了
Something is seriously wrong with me.
我不能再这么继续下去了
I can't do this anymore.
我不能在
I can't keep smiling
所有证据都指向相反面时
and being optimistic all the time
还面带微笑  假装乐观了
when all the evidence points to the contrary.
你真心认为三年以后
You really think that three years from now
情况不会变得更好吗
things aren't gonna be awesome?
让我来告诉你
I'll tell you what things are gonna be like
三年之后的情形吧
three years from now.
你好
Uh, yes, hello. I see
我从冷冻食品上看到可以打这个号码
on my frozen entree for one they printed this number
发表我的评论和意见
where I can voice comments and concerns.
这盒酥皮水果馅饼里的肉桂  比平时放得多
Well, there's more cinnamon in the cobbler than usual.
不  我挺喜欢肉桂的
No, I like cinnamon.
没事  这是我应该做的
Oh, you're very welcome for my comment.
等等  别挂电话
Wait! Uh, don't go.
那个...  你喜欢肉桂吗
Um... do you like cinnamon?
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
马修  你想一起看《星球大战》吗
Marshall, you want to watch Star Wars?
抱歉  来不了了  老兄
No, can do, old bean!
我们正在鳕鱼角附近航行呢
You see, we're up on the Cape
美国东北部马萨诸塞州伸入大西洋的一个半岛
过着你憧憬已久的
living the idyllic family lifestyle
田园式的生活哦
that you've always dreamed of.
我又怀上了第五个宝宝啦
Oh, and I'm pregnant with baby #5!
你的第四个宝宝还在肚子里呢
But baby #4 isn't even out yet.
哥就是这么霸气
I'm just that good!
等一下
Oh, oh, hold on.
还有人想跟你打招呼
There's somebody wants to say hello to you.
你好啊  泰德
Hey, Ted.
我要说的是  一切都好极了
I just wanted to say that things are great,
我和那个潮帽的人渣结婚了
and I'm married to that douchey guy in the trucker hat.
你好啊  哥们儿
Whassup, bra?
原来除了你之外
It turns out it was just you
我和谁都愿意步入婚姻
I didn't want to commit to.
而且我也有后胸了哦
and I got back boobs.
真是幸福美满呀
So things are great!
回见啰
Buh-bye!
对了  泰德  这位是梅勒妮
By the way, Ted, this is Melanie.
以后你们会常常见到她的
You'll be seeing a lot more of Melanie.
等  等  等一下
Wait-wait-wait a minute!
梅勒妮是谁啊
Who is Melanie?
得了吧  巴尼  我唯一坚信
Come on, Barney, if there's one thing
不会改变的事
I can count on not to change,
就是你搂着陌生女孩走出来
it's you walking in with some random girl on your arm.
不  不  我才不要这样
No. No, I don't want that.
人生头一次
For the first time in my life,
我不愿意看到自己三年后
I don't want to find myself
还游荡在花丛中
in three years with some random girl,
不管这"花"长了几颗大胸
no matter how many boobs she has.
我只想跟昆茵在一起
I want to be with Quinn.
各位
Guys...
以后你们会常常见到昆茵的
you're gonna be seeing a lot more of Quinn.
兄弟  我们去过情欲小野猫舞厅
Dude, we've been to the Lusty Leopard.
早就全"见"光了
We've seen plenty.
我真是挖坑往里跳  好  回见
I kind of walked into that one. All right, bye-bye.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我们同居了  我很开心
We're living together, I'm excited about it,
所以我要丢掉我的杯子
and I'm getting rid of my mugs.
那是我的杯子
That was mine.
抱歉  我分不清哪只是我的  哪只是你的
Sorry. I don't know which are which.
实话实说  我从没在家泡过咖啡
Truth is, I never drink coffee at home.
这支是我的吗
This one?
好
There!
我不需要自己的杯子  因为我有你的
I don't need my coffee mugs 'cause I got yours!
下半辈子都用你的
For the rest of my life.
或直到...你不要我的那一天
Or as... long as you'll have me.
我们还没认真讨论过未来
We haven't really talked about the future.
我是不是把事情弄得尴尬了
Did I make things awkward?
继续摔你的杯子吧
Just keep smashing mugs.
也可以把它们捐了
Or donate them.
问题是
Point is,
我打算和你长相厮守
I plan on being with you for a long time.
你对此有意见吗
You okay with that?
听起来还不错
Sounds great.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
没关系  挺好的
No, no, it's great.
男人就先"放"开啊
A guy has to be the first one to let 'er rip.
其实我一直希望这事早点发生
I was actually hoping this would happen soon.
我都躲在阳台上悄悄放屁好几周了
I've been crop-dusting the patio for weeks.
阳台呀
The patio!
我都是去街上
I've been going out on the street,
每天晚上  就在这个时间
like, exactly this time every night.
金发男  你在哪里
Where are you, blond man?!
快快现身
Show yourself!
我回娘家了
I will be at my mother's.
我们现在是真正的情侣了  对吧
We're a real couple now, aren't we?
没错
We are.
兄弟  我知道你很沮丧
Hey, buddy, I get that you're bummed.
可我预感2015会有好事发生
But I got a good feeling about 2015.
那一定会是"泰德年"
I think that's gonna be your year.
孩子们  那是我唯一一次对于
Kids, that was the one time I ever lost faith
"未来三年我会过得更好"这件事失去信心
in the idea that my life would be better in three years.
有趣的是  三年之后
And what's funny is, three years from that moment,
我的人生变得妙不可言
my life was amazing.
(现实情况)
好  又到三部曲时刻了
All right! It's trilogy time!
我能发表一下抗议吗
Can I just lodge one complaint?
这可是我们男子汉的传统
This is a guy's tradition.
泰德居然带个妞来  大煞风景啊
It's kind of a lame move on Ted's part to bring a chick.
算了  放过他吧
Come on, dude... cut him some slack.
我明白  他深爱着她
I know. He loves her.
而且她也太他妈可爱了吧
And I'll give him this: she is pretty damn cute.
幸好她长相随她妈
Thank God she takes after her mother.
好  开播吧
All right, let's watch this thing!
电视机
TV...
播放星战三部曲
play Star Wars trilogy.
播放星战三部
Play Star Wars tril...
算了  不试了
You know what? Screw it.
你即将看到画面  很精彩哟
Okay, you are about to see something awesome.
而且记住
And just know this:
是韩先开枪
Han shot first.
星球大战中  韩·索罗与格里多在剧中谁先开枪
曾出现过3个版本  各有支持者
我很好奇  等2018年再看三部曲时
I wonder if things'll be a lot different
情况会不会变得大不一样
when we watch the trilogy again in 2018.
我希望一切不要变
I hope not.
爽翻天啊
Oh, that was awesome.
-你说得对  一点都不奇怪  -是的
- You were right-- not weird. - No.